Finding Aid for Episcopal Church, Diocese of Western Michigan records, 1851-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Bishops' Files
  - Edward L. Lee
    - Topical Files, 1989-2002
      - Episcopal Church Center, 1989-2002 (Box 86)
        (include some material dated in the 1970s)
      - Episcopal Church Foundation, 1981-1996 (Box 86)
      - Episcopal Churchmen's Association, 1965-1968 (Box 86)
      - Episcopal Church Women (ECW), 1967-1998 (Box 87)
      - Episcopal Search, 1988-1989; 2001 (Box 87)
      - Evaluation of the Bishop, 1991 (Box 87)
      - Evaluation of the Diocese, 1974-1975 (Box 87)
      - Evangelical Lutheran Church of America, 1998-2000 (Box 87)
      - Evangelism (Dept. of) and evangelism (miscellaneous), 1970-1989 (Box 87)
      - Executive Council Meeting files
        - 1989-1993 (Box 88)
        - 1994-1996 (Box 89)
        - 1997-2001 (Box 90)
      - Executive Council Topical
        (include administrative miscellanea and planning retreats, etc.)
        - Administrative Plan (Subcommittee on the), 1992-1997 (Box 90)
        - Administrative Plan (Committee on the), 1998-2001 (Box 90)
        - Forms (Box 90)
        - General, correspondence and minute drafts, 1968-1971 (Box 90)
        - In-Between Mailing, 1998 (Box 90)
        - New Member Orientation, 1995-1996 (Box 91)
        - Planning Weekend, 1998-2001 (Box 91)
      - F (miscellaneous) (Box 91)
      - Faith Alive Weekend, 1981-1989 (Box 91)
      - Finance Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 91)
      - Fund Raising for Cathedral, 1968-1970 (Box 91)
      - G (miscellaneous) (Box 91)
      - General Board of Examining Chaplains, 1957-2000 (Box 91)
      - General Convention, 1991-2000 (Box 92)
      - Grant applications/funding requests (Box 92)
      - Grassroots Episcopal Environmental Network, 1993-1996 (Box 92)
      - Guidelines (marriage, etc.), 1995-1996 (Box 92)
      - H (miscellaneous) (Box 92)
      - Historiographer, 1990-1994 (Box 92)
      - Hospice proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 92)
      - House of Bishops
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 92)
        - Human Sexuality, 1994-1995 (Box 92)
          (regarding statement of Koinonia and Bishop Spong)
        - Kanuga meeting, 1998 (Box 92)
        - Portland meeting, 1995 (Box 92)
      - Human sexuality, 1991-2000 (Box 92)
        (regarding in part ordination of gay clergy)
      - I (miscellaneous) (Box 93)
      - Inclusive language, 1990-1991 (Box 93)
      - Integrity (lesbian-gay ministry), 1989-1993 (Box 93)
      - Interim ministry and workshop, 1984-1999 (Box 93)
      - J (miscellaneous) (Box 93)
      - Journey to Adulthood (program for youth), 1994-1998 (Box 93)
      - Jubilee Ministry, 1983-1996 (Box 93)
      - Justice, Peace, and Integrity of Creation Commission, 1997-2002 (Box 93)
      - K (miscellaneous) (Box 93)
      - L (miscellaneous) (Box 93)
      - Leadership Academy for New Directions (L.A.N.D.), 1985-1986 (Box 93)
      - Lee, Bishop Edward
        - Installation and seating, 1989 (Box 93)
        - Interview, 1994 (Box 93)
      - Library, 1991 (Box 93)
      - Liturgical Service for the Ending of a Pastoral Relationship, 1996 (Box 93)
      - Living Stones Diocesan Partnership, 2001 (Box 93)
      - Lutheran-Episcopal Concordant, 1996 (Box 93)
      - Lutherans, Anglicans and Roman Catholics (LARC) covenant, 2001 (Box 93)
      - Lutherans, Anglicans and Roman Catholics (LARC), 1980-1985 (Box 93)
      - M (miscellaneous) (Box 93)
      - Mailings (various), 1990-1995 (Box 93)
      - Marriage (various), 1977-1981 (Box 93)
      - McGehee Fund, 1998-2000 (Box 93)
      - Michigan Church Leaders Forum, 1991-1997 (Box 93)
      - Michigan Council of Churches, 1965-1977 (Box 93)
      - Michigan Ecumenical Forum Coordinating Committee, 1990-1999 (Box 94)
      - Michigan Episcopal Dioceses Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 94)
      - Middle East (Persian Gulf) situation, 1990 (Box 94)
      - Midwest Ministry Development Service (Midwest Career Development Service), 1989-2003 (Box 94)
      - Ministry Area Profile for St. Philip's Episcopal Church, Grand Rapids, 1995 (Box 94)
      - Mutual Ministry Review, 1999 (Box 94)
      - N (miscellaneous) (Box 94)
      - Nashotah House (Episcopal theological seminary), 1985-1990 (Box 94)
      - National Patterns (overview of the Episcopal Church), 1993 (Box 94)
      - New clergy orientation, 1995-2000 (Box 94)
      - New Person ministry, 1998 (Box 94)
      - Nigeria (companion dioceses of Ondo and Kwara), 1987-1998 (Box 94)
      - Non-Parochial Reports, 1990-2001 (Box 94)
      - P (miscellaneous) (Box 94)
      - Parish mailings, 1995-2001 (Box 95)
      - Parish Parochial audits, 2000-2001 (Box 95)
      - Parish Support Committee, 1987-1995 (Box 95)
      - Parish support staff mailings, 1995-2001 (Box 95)
      - Pastoral Letter Drafting Commission, 1988-1993 (Box 95)
        (regarding racial inclusiveness)
      - Pastoral letters, 1984-1992 (Box 95)
      - Prospects for Ministry, 1950s; 1960s (Box 95)
      - Press Conference, 1989-1992 (Box 95)
        (regarding concern about political and social issues)
      - Province V (Province V Synod), 1997-2001 (Box 95)
      - R (miscellaneous) (Box 95)
      - S (miscellaneous) (Box 95)
      - St. Aidan's Chapel (WMU student ministry), 1985-1992 (Box 96)
      - Season of Creation, 1996 (Box 96)
      - Sexual misconduct: Policies and prevention, 1994-2001 (Box 96)
      - Spiritual Directors, 1994-2000 (Box 96)
      - T (miscellaneous) (Box 96)
      - Task Force
        - Communications, 1994-1998 (Box 96)
        - Racism, Task Force on, 1993-1996 (Box 96)
        - Realignment of the Diocese of Michigan and Western Diocese, 1989-1990 (Box 96)
        - Status of Women (Box 96)
      - Teaching Day, 1994-1999 (Box 96)
      - Total Ministry Oversight Committee, 1993-2002 (Box 96)
      - Total Ministry Oversight Committee (cont.), 1993-2002 (Box 97)
      - U (miscellaneous) (Box 97)
      - United Thank Offering (UTO), 1991-1999 (Box 97)
      - Urban Bishops Coalition, 1980s-1990s (Box 97)
      - Vestry List, 1994-1995 (Box 97)
      - Vestry Workshop, 1994-1995 (Box 97)
      - Visitation (Bishop's) material, 1997 (Box 97)
      - W (miscellaneous) (Box 97)
      - Wardens and treasurers, 1997 (Box 97)
      - Wyoming, Holy Trinity Church, 1979-1998 (Box 97)
      - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 97)
      - Year of Identity, 1991 (Box 97)
      - Youth Camp, 1996-1998 (Box 97)
      - Youth and Violence Subcommittee (Box 97)
      - Youth (miscellaneous), 1997-2002 (Box 97)
      - Z (miscellaneous) (Box 97)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 97)
  - Robert R. Gepert
    The Bishop Gepert sub-series, arranged alphabetically, in addition to its documentation of the Executive Council and the Diocesan Conventions, also includes extensive material relating to the church's anti-racism initiatives.
    - Topical Files
      - Anti-Racism Task Force and related, 5 folders (Box 110)
      - Bishop Whittemore Foundation, 2003-2006 (Box 110)
      - Cathedral Corporation, 2003-2007 (Box 110)
      - Cathedral Study Committee (Box 110)
      - Cathedral Sales Agreement and related material, 2007 (Box 110)
      - Cathedral School (Box 110)
      - Clergy Mailings, 2003-2005; 4 folders (Box 110)
      - Commission on Ministry
        - 1997-1999 (Box 110)
        - 2000 (Box 110)
        - 2001 (Box 110)
        - 2002, 2 folders (Box 111)
        - Miscellaneous: include Total Ministry Curriculum (Box 111)
      - Diocesan Convention, 2002-2005; 5 folders (Box 111)
      - Executive Council (multiple folders), 2002-2005 (Box 111)
- Chancellor
  The Chancellor series includes topical files of Charles L. Dibble, Burritt Hamilton, and Niel Weathers. These files are either arranged alphabetically by topic or chronologically if miscellaneous material. The series covers the period from 1925 to 1963.
  - Charles L. Dibble
    - Topical File
      - Akeley Hall, 1926-1933; 2 folders (Box 49)
      - Benton Harbor, 1939 (Box 49)
      - Big Rapids, 1939 (Box 49)
      - Bishop, James Horton, 1929-1933 (Box 49)
      - Canons, Revision, 1926-1927 (Box 49)
      - Coldwater, 1932; 1939 (Box 49)
      - Diocesan Assessments, 1927-1932; 2 folders (Box 49)
      - Diocesan Conventions, 1933-1938; 3 folders (Box 49)
      - Dowagiac, 1926-1927; 1930-1939; 2 folders (Box 49)
      - Gorham, F.A., 1931-1932 (Box 49)
      - Grand Ledge, 1928 (Box 49)
      - Grand Rapids (St. Philip's), 1928 (Box 49)
      - Harbor Springs, 1939 (Box 49)
      - Homer, 1927 (Box 49)
      - Incorporation of Parishes, 1938 (Box 49)
      - Investment of Trust Funds, 1939 (Box 49)
      - Marriages and Annulments, 1938-1939 (Box 49)
      - Mendon, 1936-1940; 3 folders (Box 49)
      - National Council Report, 1926 (Box 49)
      - Paw Paw, 1931-1934 (Box 49)
      - Proposed Law, 1937 (Box 49)
      - Saugatuck, 1935-1937; 2 folders (Box 49)
      - Stevens, Vernette, 1926 (Box 49)
      - Taxation of Bishop's House, 1928 (Box 49)
      - Taxes, 1938 (Box 49)
      - Tustin Trust fund, 1937 (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous Papers
      - 1925-1929, 5 folders (Box 49)
      - 1930-1940, 18 folders (Box 50)
  - Burritt Hamilton
    - Papers, 1940-1954; 12 folders (Box 50)
  - Niel Weathers
    - Papers, 1954-1963; 8 folders (Box 51)
- Treasurer
  The Treasurer series contains topical files of diocesan treasurers Harry C. Angell and Norman A. Lilly. Arranged alphabetically, these subseries span the period from 1925-1939.
  - Harry C. Angell
    - Akeley Hall, 1928-1932; 6 folders (Box 51)
    - Church Finance Board, 1926-1930 (Box 51)
    - Church Helper, 1927-1932; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Executive Council Proceedings, 1925-1932 (Box 51)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1927-1930; 7 folders (Box 51)
    - Ionia Pensions, 1926-1927 (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous, 1928-1932 (Box 51)
    - National Council, 1928-1932 (Box 51)
    - National Treasurer, 1928-1932; 3 folders (Box 51)
    - Parish Promises, 1926-1932 (Box 51)
    - Pension Fund, 1925-1929; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Pension, 1930-1932 (Box 51)
    - Reports to the Diocesan Convention, 1929-1932 (Box 51)
    - Reports to the Executive Council, 1928-1932; 5 folders (Box 52)
    - Stevens Farm, 1928-1930 (Box 52)
    - Stevens, Sydney F., 1931-1932 (Box 52)
    - Wilkinson, James E., 1930-1932 (Box 52)
  - Norman A. Lilly
    - Audits, 1932-1935 (Box 52)
    - Bishop Coadjutor, 1935-1936 (Box 52)
    - Church Pension Fund, 1933-1936 (Box 52)
    - Everyman's Campaign, 1934; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Field Department Chairman, 1935-1936 (Box 52)
    - Finance Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 52)
    - Grand Rapids (Grace Church), 1936 (Box 52)
    - McCormick, John (Bishop), 1933-1936 (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous, 1933-1936; 6 folders (Box 52)
    - National Council, 1933-1939; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Trustees of the Diocese, 1936 (Box 52)
    - Steven's Farm, 1934-1935 (Box 52)
    - Women's Auxiliary, 1932-1936 (Box 52)
- Diocesan Historiographer
  Another strength of the record group is its documentation of numerous local Episcopal parishes and missions in western Michigan. The files of the Diocesan Historiographer, the officer responsible for collecting historical information on diocesan churches, together with the correspondence files of the other diocesan offices document local parish activities, largely from about 1930 to the 1980s. Included in the collection is the manuscript copy and additional notes for Rev. Franklin Smith's history The Diocese of Western Michigan. This volume provides a thorough history of the diocese to 1948 and should be consulted as background to the archival records. This series also includes files of historiographer Maurice F. Thomas and Betty Sutton. Within the Betty Sutton subseries, in addition to collected material on the individual parishes, there is an extensive set of files with biographical information on the priests of the diocese.
  - Rev. Franklin Smith
    - History-The Diocese of Western Michigan
      - Manuscript, undated; 11 folders (Box 53)
      - Papers, chapters 1-20, undated; 23 folders (Box 53)
      - Papers, undated, chapters 20-22, 2 folders (Box 54)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 6 folders (Box 54)
      - Correspondence, 1939-1945; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Collected historical materials
      - Reminiscences of the Rev. James E. Wilkinson, undated (Box 54)
      - Papers concerning Bishop George D. Gillespie, undated (Box 54)
      - Papers concerning the Rev. Luman Foote, undated (Box 54)
      - Pamphlet concerning St. Mark's College and schools in Grand Rapids, 1850 (Box 54)
    - Parish and Mission Historical and Background Information
      - Albion (Box 54)
      - Allegan (Box 54)
      - Battle Creek (Box 54)
      - Big Rapids (Box 54)
      - Charlevoix (Box 54)
      - Charlotte (Box 54)
      - Coldwater (Box 54)
      - Elk Rapids (Box 54)
      - Grand Haven (Box 54)
      - Grand Rapids
        - Grace Church (Box 54)
        - St. Mark's (Box 54)
        - St. Paul's (Box 54)
      - Greenville (Box 54)
      - Harbor Springs (Box 54)
      - Hastings (Box 54)
      - Holland (Box 54)
      - Homer (Box 54)
      - Ionia (Box 54)
      - Kalamazoo (Box 54)
      - Ludington (Box 54)
      - Lyons (Box 54)
      - Manistee (Box 54)
      - Marshall (Box 54)
      - Mendon (Box 54)
      - Mount Pleasant (Box 54)
      - Muskegon (Box 54)
      - Paw Paw (Box 54)
      - Petoskey (Box 54)
      - Plainfield (Box 54)
      - St. Joseph (Box 54)
      - Saugatuck (Box 54)
      - South Haven (Box 54)
      - Sturgis (Box 54)
      - Three Rivers (Box 54)
  - Maurice F. Thomas
    - Reports, etc.
      - Annual Conventions, 1955-1965 (Box 55)
      - Annual Reports of Registrar and Historiographer, 1952-1972 (Box 55)
      - Cathedral Construction, 1967-1969 (Box 55)
      - Constitution and Canons of the Diocese, 1956-1966 (Box 55)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960-1972 (Box 55)
    - Parish and Mission Historical Materials
      - Annual Rosters, Parish and Mission Historians, 1953-1970 (Box 55)
      - Ada-Cascade (Box 55)
      - Albion (Box 55)
      - Allegan (Box 55)
      - Battle Creek (Box 55)
      - Beaver Island (Box 55)
      - Benton Harbor (Box 55)
      - Benzie County (Box 55)
      - Big Rapids (Box 55)
      - Cadillac (Box 55)
      - Charlevoix (Box 55)
      - Charlotte (Box 55)
      - Coldwater (Box 55)
      - Conway (Box 55)
      - Dowagiac (Box 55)
      - Elk Rapids (Box 55)
      - Grand Haven (Box 55)
      - Grand Ledge (Box 55)
      - Grand Rapids
        - Good Shepherd Church (Box 55)
        - Grace Church (Box 55)
        - Holy Cross (Box 55)
        - St. Andrew's (Box 55)
        - St. Mark's (Box 55)
        - St. Paul's (Box 55)
      - Greenville (Box 55)
      - Harbor Springs (Box 55)
      - Hastings (Box 55)
      - Holland (Box 55)
      - Ionia (Box 55)
      - Kalamazoo
        - St. Luke's (Box 55)
        - St. Martin's (Box 55)
      - Lakeside (Box 55)
      - Lansing (Box 55)
      - Lee Township (Box 55)
      - Ludington (Box 55)
      - Manistee (Box 55)
      - Marshall (Box 55)
      - Montague-Whitehall (Box 55)
      - Mt. Pleasant (Box 55)
      - Muskegon
        - St. Alban's (Box 55)
        - St. Gregory's (Box 55)
        - St. Paul's (Box 55)
      - Newaygo (Box 55)
      - Niles (Box 55)
      - Onekama (Box 55)
      - Orangeville (Box 55)
      - Paw Paw (Box 55)
      - Pentwater (Box 55)
      - Plainfield (Box 55)
      - Plainwell (Box 55)
      - Portage (Box 55)
      - Richland (Box 55)
      - Rockford (Box 55)
      - Saugatuck (Box 55)
      - South Haven (Box 55)
      - Sparta (Box 55)
      - St. Joseph (Box 55)
      - Sturgis (Box 55)
      - Three Rivers
        - St. Gregory's Priory (Box 55)
        - Trinity Church (Box 55)
      - Traverse City (Box 55)
      - Wyoming (Box 55)
  - Betty Sutton
    - History and Related
      - Celebratory programs (Box 103)
      - Diocese history, 1998 (Box 103)
      - Correspondence (Box 103)
      - Clippings (Box 103)
    - Parish and Mission Historical Materials
      Photographs throughout as indicated
      - Albion. St. James (Box 103)
      - Allegan. Good Shepherd (Box 103)
        (include photograph)
      - Baldwin. St. Matthew's (Box 103)
      - Battle Creek.
        - Resurrection (Box 103)
        - St. Thomas (Box 103)
          (include photographs)
      - Beaver Island. St. James (Box 103)
      - Beldin's. Trinity (Box 103)
      - Bellaire. St. Sebaldus (Box 103)
      - Benton Harbor.
        - Holy Trinity (Box 103)
        - St. Augustine (Box 103)
        - St. Stephen's (Box 103)
      - Benzie County. St. Philips (Box 103)
      - Big Rapids. St. Andrews (Box 103)
      - Buchanan. St. Andrew's (Box 103)
      - Burr Oak. Grace (Box 103)
      - Cadillac.
        - Holy Trinity (Box 103)
        - St. Mary's (Box 103)
      - Cascade. St. Michael's (Box 103)
      - Cassopolis. St. James (Box 103)
      - Central Lake. St. Matthew's (Box 103)
      - Charlevoix. Christ Church (Box 103)
      - Charlotte.
        - Grace (Box 103)
        - St. John's (Box 103)
      - Clare. St. Paul's (Box 103)
      - Coldwater. St. Mark's (Box 103)
      - Constantine. St. James (Box 103)
      - Coopersville. Epiphany (Box 103)
      - Coopersville. St. Mark's (Box 103)
      - Dowagiac.
        - St. Alban (Box 103)
        - St. Paul's (Box 103)
      - East Jordan. Redeemer (Box 103)
      - Eaton Rapids. St. Matthew's (Box 103)
      - Edwardsburg. St. Stephen's (Box 103)
      - Elk Rapids. St. Paul's (Box 103)
      - Evart. St. John's (Box 103)
      - Farwell. Trinity (Box 103)
      - Fremont. St. John's (Box 103)
      - Grand Haven. St. John's (Box 103)
      - Grand Ledge.
        - St. Andrew's (Box 103)
        - Trinity (Box 103)
      - Grand Rapids.
        - Good Shepherd (Box 103)
        - Grace (Box 103)
        - St. Andrew's (Box 103)
        - St. Bede's (Box 103)
        - St. John's (Box 103)
        - St. Mark's (Box 103)
        - St. Matthew's (Box 103)
        - St. Stephen's (Box 103)
        - Trinity (Box 103)
      - Greenville. St. Paul's (Box 103)
      - Harbor Springs. St. John's (Box 103)
      - Hart. St. Andrew's (Box 103)
      - Hastings. Emmanuel (Box 103)
      - Hershey. Grace (Box 103)
      - Holland. Grace (Box 103)
      - Homer. Christ (Box 103)
      - Howard City. Calvary (Box 103)
      - Ionia. St. John's (Box 103)
      - Kalamazoo.
        - Acension (Box 103)
        - Cathedral (Box 103)
        - St. John's (Box 103)
        - St. Luke's (Box 103)
      - Kentwood. Holy Cross (Box 103)
      - Lansing, St. David's (Box 103)
      - Lawton. St. John's (Box 103)
      - Lee Township. St. Michael's All Angels (Box 103)
      - Leland. St. Peter's (Box 103)
      - Ludington. Grace (Box 103)
      - Luther. Christ (Box 103)
      - Lyons. Grace (Box 103)
        (include some Women’s Guild records, 1920s-1930s)
      - Mancelona. Church of the Nativity (Box 103)
      - Manistee.
        - Grace (Box 103)
        - Holy Trinity (Box 103)
        - St. Paul's (Box 103)
      - Marshall. Trinity (Box 103)
      - Mendon. St. Paul's (Box 103)
      - Montague. St. Peter's (Box 103)
      - Mount Pleasant. St. John's (Box 103)
      - Muskegon.
        - St. Alban's (Box 104)
        - St. Gregory's (Box 104)
        - St. Luke's (Box 104)
        - St. Paul's (Box 104)
      - Newaygo. St. Mark's (Box 104)
      - Niles. Trinity (Box 104)
      - Northpoint. Atwell Chapel (Box 104)
      - Northport. St. Christopher (Box 104)
      - Onekama. St. John-by-the-Lake (Box 104)
      - Orangeville. St. Francis (Box 104)
        (includes photo postcard)
      - Paw Paw. St. Mark's, 4 folders (Box 104)
      - Pentwater. St. James (Box 104)
      - Petoskey. Emmanuel (Box 104)
      - Plainwell. St. Stephen's (Box 104)
      - Portage. St. Barnabas (Box 104)
      - Portland. St. Paul's (Box 104)
      - Quincy. St. John's (Box 104)
      - Richland. St. Timothy's (Box 104)
      - Rockford. James (Box 104)
      - Saranac. Trinity (Box 104)
      - Saugatuck. All Saints (Box 104)
      - Schoolcraft. St. Stephen's (Box 104)
      - South Haven.
        - Epiphany (Box 104)
        - Trinity (Box 104)
      - Sparta. St. Matthew's (Box 104)
      - St. Joseph.
        - Christ (Box 104)
        - St. Paul's (Box 104)
        - St. Peter's (Box 104)
      - Sturgis. St. James (Box 104)
      - Sturgis. St. John's (Box 104)
      - Three Rivers. Trinity (Box 104)
      - Traverse City. Grace (Box 104)
      - Union City. Grace (Box 104)
      - Vicksburg. St. Andrew's (Box 104)
      - Whitehall. Church of the Redeemer (Box 104)
      - Wyoming. Holy Trinity (Box 104)
    - Clergy, biographical and related materials
      - Abraham, John Laurence (Box 104)
      - Adams, Harold Beach (Box 104)
      - Adams, Hiram (Box 104)
      - Adams, Percy C. (Box 104)
      - Adams, Richard S. (Box 104)
      - Aldrich, Thomas Bailey (Box 104)
      - Aldworth, Edward Letellier (Box 104)
      - Allabaugh, B. R. (Box 104)
      - Allen, A. W. (Box 104)
      - Allen, J. Ethan (Box 104)
      - Allen, James Richard (Box 104)
      - Almquist, Peter Auguste (Box 104)
      - Ames, Roger Copeland (Box 104)
      - Anderson, F. E. B. (Box 104)
      - Anderson, George B. (Box 104)
      - Anderson, Jesse F. (Box 104)
      - Anderson, Joseph Randolph (Box 104)
      - Anderson, Scott James (Box 104)
      - Anderson, Vincent J. (Box 104)
      - Andrews, Robert Forrest (Box 104)
      - Armstrong, Jean Weslau (Box 104)
      - Aspen, Samuel Campbell Montgomery (Box 104)
      - Atamian, Thomas M. (Box 104)
      - Atwell, Charles D. (Box 104)
      - Atwill, Edward Robert (Box 104)
      - Austin, Joseph Perry (Box 104)
      - Avery, Richard Noyes (Box 104)
      - Ayres, George W. Sinclair (Box 104)
      - Ayres, Phillip W. (Box 104)
      - Babcock, Eugene Jeffery (Box 104)
      - Babcock, Isaiah J. (Box 104)
      - Babcock, John Henry, Jr. (Box 104)
      - Bachman, W. Fenwick (Box 104)
      - Bain, Caroline M. (Box 104)
      - Baird, Robert Lee (Box 104)
      - Baker, Richard G. (Box 104)
      - Baldwin, John Anson (Box 104)
      - Bancroft, Joseph Webb (Box 104)
      - Banwell, Henry (Box 104)
      - Barkdull, Edward S. (Box 105)
      - Barker, Darius (Box 105)
      - Barnhart, Arthur Clinton (Box 105)
      - Barr, Preston (Box 105)
      - Basso, Louis, Jr. (Box 105)
      - Batchelder, Edwin Armstrong (Box 105)
      - Bateman, William Jones (Box 105)
      - Bates, Carroll Lund (Box 105)
      - Baynton, James A. (Box 105)
      - Bean, Seward Henry (Box 105)
      - Beardsley, Charles E. (Box 105)
      - Beckwith, Sidney (Box 105)
      - Bedford-Jones, Wilford J. William (Box 105)
      - Beeson, Thomas (Box 105)
      - Belcher, E. C. (Box 105)
      - Bell, Robert Craig (Box 105)
      - Benedict, Durlin Serenus (Box 105)
      - Benjamin, Heber C. (Box 105)
      - Bennett, Beasley Woodrow (Box 105)
      - Bennett, Charles Gibson (Box 105)
      - Bennett, Roscoe Dudley (Box 105)
      - Bennett, Walter McDade (Box 105)
      - Bennison, Charles Ellsworth (Box 105)
      - Bierlein, Raymond E. (Box 105)
      - Bigler, Cleon E. (Box 105)
      - Birch, Lewis Cass (Box 105)
      - Bishop, Addis E. (Box 105)
      - Bishop, Charles E. (Box 105)
      - Bishop, J. Frederick (Box 105)
      - Bishop, James Horton (Box 105)
      - Bissell, Rev. (Box 105)
      - Black, Cynthia L. (Box 105)
      - Blackburn, Glen A. (Box 105)
      - Blake, Wallace Herbert (Box 105)
      - Blakeslee, Clyde B. (Box 105)
      - Blaske, Drayton Royal (Box 105)
      - Blunt, Forest Hayden (Box 105)
      - Boardman, Norman Smith (Box 105)
      - Boeve, Phillip D. (Box 105)
      - Bohmer, Karl J. (Box 105)
      - Bowling, Jack D. (Box 105)
      - Bradford, Richard Sterling (Box 105)